MAN:
May I help you?
(Sheldon:)Um...
(Leonard:)Uh, uh... we don't
have an appointment,
and-and we don't
belong here,
but we-we're, like,
crazy-big fans.
(Penny:)I mean...
(stammers)
"crazy for Star
Wars" crazy,
(Leonard:)not crazy like we have a
backpack full of duct tape,
(Leonard:)although we do
have a backpack
(Leonard:)that you really don't
want to look in.
(Sheldon:)You're blowing it.
(Sheldon:)We want to meet
George Lucas
(Sheldon:)and become his friends
and play with him!
(Voice:)Hello?
(Voice:)This speaker's not working,
just pull up.
(Leonard:)And that's how it's done.
(Sheldon:)All right, we've defeated
the first challenge.
(Sheldon:)Now we must steel ourselves
to face the monster
(Sheldon:)who defends the gate.